Guide to the John H. Whitlock papers, 1937-1977,
Whitlock, John H. papers
- Board of Trustees Financial (Budgets)
  - Fiscal Information - Ex. Comm., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Financial Information - General, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Financial Investment Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Summary of Managed Funds, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Trustee Ad Hoc Comm. on Capital Financing, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Year End Closing, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Ex. Comm. Reports and Recommendations, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Cornell University Senate
  - Agendas, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bills
    - B Series, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - C Series, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - D Series, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - E Series, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - F Series, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - G Series, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - C.U. Faculty Handbook, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Constituent Assembly, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Bills - SA Series and SG Series, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    - Bill Drafting and Legislative Procedure, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Senate Bylaws, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Campus Planning Comm. - Campus Life, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Division of Campus Life, Budgets, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16-18)
    - Campus Planning Comm., 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Senate Chronicle, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Comm. on Codes and Judiciary, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Comm. on Internal Operation, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Senate Constitution, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Speaker - Robert Cooke, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Credentials Committee Report, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Election Results, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - William Gurowitz - V.P. Campus Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - General, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Legislative Procedures; Robert's Rules of Order; Senate Quorum, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Physical Education, Graduation Requirement, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Names and Addresses of Senators, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Semester Schedule, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - R.O.T.C., 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Secretariat, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Student Rights, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - C.U. Unions - Supplementary Data, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - William White - Chairman of Ex. Comm., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Proposals, Legislation, etc., 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 39-40)
  - Minutes
    - Vol. VII, No. 2, 1976-03-23 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vol. VII, No. 1, 1976-03-09 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vol. VI, No. 1, 1975-03-04 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vol. V., No. 7, 1974-09-10 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vol, V, No. 6, 1974-05-07 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vol. V, No. 5, 1974-04-30 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Vol. V, No. 4, 1974-04-17 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Vol. V, No. 3, 1974-04-02 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Vol. V, No. 2, 1974-03-26 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Vol. V, No. 1, 1974-03-14 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Vol. IV, No. 13, 1974-01-29 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Memo, 1974-01-22 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 11, 1973-12-04 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 10, 1973-11-27 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 9, 1973-11-06 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 8, 1973-10-23 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 7, 1973-10-09 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 6, 1973-09-11 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vol. IV, No. 5, 1973-05-01 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vol. IV, No. 4, 1973-04-24 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vol. IV, No. 3, 1973-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vol. IV, No. 2, 1973-04-03 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vol. IV, No. 1, 1973-03-13 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vol. III, No. 16, 1973-02-27 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Vol. III, No. 15, 1973-02-20 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Vol. III, No. 14, 1973-02-13 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Vol. III, No. 13, 1973-02-06 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Vol. III, No. 12, 1973-01-23 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Vol. III, No. 11, 1972-12-05 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vol. III, No. 10, 1972-11-28 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vol. III, No. 9, 1972-11-14 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vol. III, No. 8, 1972-11-09 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vol. III, No. 7, 1972-10-31 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vol. III, No. 6, 1972-10-03 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vol. III, No. 5, 1972-05-02 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vol. III, No. 4, 1972-04-25 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vol. II, No. 21, 1972-02-29 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vol. II, No. 20, 1972-02-22 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vol. II, No. 19, 1972-02-17 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Vol. II, No. 18, 1972-02-08 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Vol. II, No. 17, 1972-01-25 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Vol. II, No. 16, 1971-12-14 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Vol. II, No. 14, 1971-11-23 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Vol. II, No. 11, 1971-10-12 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Community Affairs Comm. - WHCU Resolution, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Min. and Dis. Int. Comm. - Penal Reform Act, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vol. II, No. 10, 1971-09-21 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vol. II, No. 9, 1971-09-07 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vol. II, No. 8, 1971-05-18 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vol. II, No. 7, 1971-05-13 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vol. I, No. 2, 1970-05-24 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Memos and Agendas, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bills - Series C and E, 1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Senate Memos, Vita, Budget, Acts, Procedures, etc., 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 6 Books - Annual Extension Report of the Dept. of Animal Husbandry, 1936-1937, 1938-1939, 1939-1940, 1940-1941, 1941-1943, 1948-1950 (Box 7)
      Count: 6
    - 15-15A; Smith-Lever Project; N.Y.S. Coll. of Agric. Cornell Univ., Undated (Box 7)